JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 5
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 3
LUXURY CONDOMINIUMS
NIJIMURA PROPERTIES CO.
THE HAND
NUMBER WITHHELD PUBLIC PHONE
NIJIMURA FAMILY
EPISODE 6
KOICHI HIROSE (REVERB)